neostencil.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | NeoStencil

Privacy Statement 

NeoStencil India Private Limited (“ **NeoStencil** ”) is committed to operating this website with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls. We are sensitive to the scenario that we would be dealing with data and information of a personal nature. By using this website and providing your personal information, you consent to the terms of our online privacy policy and to our processing of such personal information for the purposes explained in this policy. As part of our normal operations we collect, and in some cases, disclose information about you. By registering on the website or by subscribing to a service and providing your contact details (telephone, email, mobile number, shipping address, credit card details etc), you agree that this action constitutes a consent, for the purposes of the telemarketing laws, to receive information about products and services (“ **Services** ”) from NeoStencil. You hereby consent to our contacting you pursuant to the business relationship established using the information you provide to us. We encourage you to read this privacy policy regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of or your information. If you are not comfortable with any of the terms or policies described in this Privacy Policy, we ask that you discontinue use of our website. 

**SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?**

Your privacy is very important to us. We follow systematic and stringent procedures to protect the security of the information / data stored on our website. The information that you have shared on our website is stored in secure server with encryption and can be accessed only for official purposes. Any of our employees who violate our privacy and/or security policies related to customer’s data is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

**SECTION 2 – CONSENT**

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

**SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE**

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service. As per our security procedures we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

**SECTION 4 – PAYMENT**

We do not take Credit/Debit card or Net banking details on our website. On clicking the option Pay Now, you will be redirected to either Secure Payment Gateway or Bank’s Net Banking website for completing the transaction. You will then be required to enter your relevant card details or net banking details on the page to complete the transaction. On successful completion of the transaction, you will be redirected to our website with your order details and order number being displayed. It is to be noted that we will not be storing any Bank related information on our records and none of our staffs will hold or be exposed to this information.

**SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

_Links_

When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**SECTION 6 – SECURITY**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

**SECTION 7 – COOKIES**

We use cookies to maintain session of your user. It is not used to personally identify you on other websites.

**SECTION 8 – AGE OF CONSENT**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

**SECTION 9 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**SECTION 10 – QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us via email at info@neostencil.com
